# LE NGUYEN THAO NGOC Marketing Team Leader

A: Binh Thanh District, HCMC

D.O.B: 24/05/1993 | E: ngoc.\*\*\*\*\*@\*\*\*.\*\*\*.com | M: 0937 009 389



### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a smart, flexible and dynamic person. After more than three years working for a startup company - OFOOD Trading & Service Ltd.Co in Food & Beverage industry, I have gained a great deal of knowledge and experience in marketing field. In particular, I am good at team management in order to achieve company's sales targets. As a fast learner, I would adapt quickly in the new environment. Additionally, I am able to handle multitasks in the harsh environment in order to achieve goals with tight deadline.

I aim to become a seasoned marketing manager in the next 5 years and therefore, I am looking for marketing job opportunities as team leader/managerial positions in F&B/Retail/Restaurant industries to cultivate my skill set and expand my network.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### 09/2015 - 12/2018: OFOOD Trading & Service Ltd.Co

The company specializes in trading many restaurant chains of fusion concepts, including grilled chicken chain with sauce named Gà Nướng Ò Ó O, and dipping beef sauce and dip hotpot concept named Bò-lế-rổ. The company owns more than 20 stores in Saigon & Hanoi.

#### 03/2016 - 12/2018: Marketing Team Leader

## Develop and implement marketing activities for brands: Gà Nướng Ò Ó O, Bò-lế-rồ

- Develop marketing plan, execute and evaluate all marketing activities for 2 brands, including online marketing and offline marketing.
- In charge of marketing planning and annual budget management for brands.
- Follow up market trends: collect data of the market, customers and competitors, conduct data analysis to recognize the new trends, new taste from the market in order to adjust marketing strategy.
- Build up good relationship with key customers, communication partners and influencers in the F&B field (GrabFood, Foody.vn, Adayroi, Food Blogger, ect)
- Take responsibility to execute all branding campaigns, cross-marketing campaign with key partners, promotion campaigns and strategies to increase sales for 2 brands.
- · Lead internal marketing team to achieve all marketing targets.
- · Follow, evaluate, measure the value of 2 brands on the market.
- Manage the quality of all marketing products (POSM, advertising, content, designs, ...) made by the team.
- Being project leaders for all cross-functional projects related to opening and lauching of new stores and new menu.
- Conduct marketing reports and analysis to CEO & Business Development Director.

## 09/2015 - 02/2016: Marketing Assistant to CEO

· Support CEO in innovation process and analysis report.

1

- · Work closely between key customers, communication partners and influencers in the F&B field.
- · Collect competitor information and activities in the market.
- · Direct marketing management and execution.
- Support marketing team in implementing promotion programs.
- · Manage all documents (input and output) and marketing stock.
- · Conduct periodical reports to CEO.

### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- · Leadership and management skills
- · Time management and crisis management skills
- · Strategic planning on marketing & communication
- Track the progress and coordinate the work as planned

### CERTIFICATIONS

03 - 05/2019

Brand Managment Excellence - AIM Academy 05/2018

Enhance Customer Experience & Boost Profitability Tran Dinh Cuu Consulting Company Limited

06 - 09/2015

Social Media Trainee - Xanh Marketing

10/2013 - 05/2014

Project Volunteer Green Hours by Green Talk - UNESCO-CEP

### **ATTITUDE**

- · Responsible in work
- · Logical thinking and creative
- Positive attitude when faced with criticism
- Eager to learn and never afraid of difficulties

### **EDUCATION**

09/2011 - 07/2015

Van Lang University
PR & Communications Bachelor